[{"answer": "Yes, I did speak with her tonight and she did tell me that her son was OK.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "You spoke to Tameka tonight?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, from what I've read and from what information that's out currently is that the snake escaped it's enclosure, which was housed in the pet store in the first floor.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Where was this snake and how did it get out?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that would be the cause of death involving a snake, especially of that size.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Is that what we believe the cause of death is?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Could that have attracted the snake, do you think?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Piers, it's extremely helpful, these Amber alerts.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "People getting messages on their cell phones and so on to try and encourage them to see if they can see these two kids, Hanna Anderson and Ethan Anderson?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing -- one of the first things you learn in law school, Piers, any person that defends himself has a fool for a client.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Is there a sensible way of spending public money?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Not may, does.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "But what about the rights -- what about the rights, Star, of the victims that he shot who he may now have the legal right to interrogate?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Because the criminal justice system is there where the defendant is innocent, unless and until proven guilty.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "How can that be right?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "But admission of responsibility for the act is not admission of culpability under the law.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Even when he's admitted I'm the shooter?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "ONES: I know.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Do you mind if I say, this is legal gooblededoo?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "It is a necessary evil.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "So it's a necessary evil?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I wish I could say I'm surprised.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Not as much because New York is sort of my city, and I tend to go places where I'm expected.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Have you experienced it in New York?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "So you're almost subliminally avoiding it?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Absolutely, in the middle of the street.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Have you really?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "I act like they're not talking to me because it's not what they call you, it's what you answer to.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "And how do you reach when you hear that?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Yes, it's not so much that it's gotten better.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Has it gotten any better since the first black president of the United States or not?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "You know, the people whoever were in the Madison Avenue store when they saw Oprah Winfrey, they immediately thought black woman can't afford this so why am I letting her in?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Clearly, the facts and circumstances were very much different but in terms of it being pivotal and starting a discussion, and starting a turn, I think she's exactly right.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What do you think of Oprah linking the Emmett Till case to this?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "No, it's not that I think he's innocent.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "You think he's innocent?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "If you get told today that they no longer want you here at CNN, I guarantee you, you going to ask them to go through the process.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "-- did he actually say it's not true?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I will tell you, please shut up and let me do the talking.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Tell me not to?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Why are you starting with him?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I don't know what is wrong with the way Hillary looks now.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Does it matter what people are like?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "I invited her.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "I'm curious?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "You know when -- when folks leave the White House?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a very dangerous thing and not just in Libya but also in Syria.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What do you think about this?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Benghazi guy go to guy for the boobies.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "He -- he gets Benghazi and I get boobies?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I mean, look, the first amendment applies to all Americans including students in schools.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Does it matter, Josh?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "The point that I make is that goddamnit, I do think that you glorify on public television homosexuality.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Now, that's real family entertainment, isn't it?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, first great sadness given the contribution of the Graham family to journalism, to the national good health in terms of promoting a kind of reporting that serves everybody in this country, and a kind of honesty and a kind of principled management.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What is your -- your personal reaction to the fact that the Graham family that you served under for so long have finally sold out now to, you know, a -- a dot-com billionaire?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Look, it's always a tough call.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Where is the line to be drawn between what the guardians say and Glenn Greenwald and on behalf of Snowden have been doing and where the public interest lies?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I saw it in an -- in an early cut.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Did you see it by any chance?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "But did your view of Nixon -- has it changed over the years?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "No, I'm more empathy to his demons, I would say.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Do you think we're (ph) forgiving (ph) of him with history?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, what -- well, when I get to thinking about this, I've never worked a preseason where there's been more focus on the next season.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "How are you dealing with all the attention that comes with the fact you may be the first ever NFL official, female?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "They're professionals.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "I mean, what's it like when you get out there with these honking (ph) guys?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Well, I always tell them if I'm coaching them or being a mom to them, that don't ever be in a game whenever you're playing or sitting back watching and let the official make one play that you think blew the game.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Are they going to go to the football, want to instinctively shout at the referee for some terrible call and discover it's their mom?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Yes, I have.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Have you had some surprising messages of support and goodwill from people?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "No...", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "You nervous?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I really don't have any comments on that, Piers.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "What do you make of A-Rod, that little cheat down the road at the Yankees?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130806pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Do you have a favorite team -- a favorite NFL team?", "qSentId": 722}]